A Guide to the Dares Emery Wirt letters, 1946-1947
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Dares Emery Wirt letters, 1946-1947
The Library of Virginia
45313
32 leaves and 28 pages
Dares Emery Wirt
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Crown Collectibles, Chesterfield, Virginia.
Biographical Information
Dares Emery Wirt was born in 1924 in Massachusetts. He served as an officer and pilot in the United States Navy, including a stint at the Naval Auxiliary Air Station at Chincoteague, Virginia. Wirt retired as a captain in the United State Naval Reserve. He married Esther Dulin Johnson (1923-1998) in 1947, and they had at least four children.
Scope and Content
Letters, 1946-1947, from Dares Emery Wirt (1923-), stationed at the Chincoteague, Virginia, Naval Auxiliary Air Station to Esther Dulin Johnson (Wirt) (1923-1998) of St. Petersburg, Florida, detailing his duties as a Naval pilot, describing Chincoteague and surrounding communities, commenting on trips and his efforts in purchasing a car, telling Esther he misses her, and planning their wedding.
Contents List
- Letter, 16-17 October 1946. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 20 October 1946. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 25 October 1946. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 27 October 1946. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 28 October 1946. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 30 October 1946. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 20 December 1946. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 22 December 1946. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 6 January 1947. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 9 January 1947. (Folder 1)
- Letter, 14 January 1947. (Folder 2)
- Letter, 16 January 1947. (Folder 2)
- Letter, 26 January 1947. (Folder 2)
- Letter, 28 January 1947. (Folder 2)
- Letter, 30 January 1947. (Folder 2)
- Letter, 31 January[?] 1947. (Folder 2)
- Letter, 6 February 1947. (Folder 2)
- Letter, 10 February 1947. (Folder 2)
- Letter, 12 February 1947. (Folder 2)
- Letter, 17 February 1947. (Folder 2)